-[bells chime]
-[chalk scrapes]
MINISTRY OF EDUCATION
I checked everywhere.
and there's no CCTV covering the rooftop.
I did find one at the place next door
that might have caught part of it.
Can you explain while you're showing me?
-Yeah.
-Of course.
The footage is pretty bad though.
It's hard to make anything out.
Just play it.
[tense music plays]
-[Geun-dae] There! You see?
-Can you zoom in?
Yeah.
Support us and become VIP member
to remove all ads from www.OpenSubtitles.org
What if someone was behind here?
He could have been pushed off that roof.
I STAND AGAINST THE ERPB
THAT PUSHES STUDENTS TO DEATH
What are you doing here?
-Isn't it busy at the Bureau right now?
-Yeah. but it's even busier in my head.
I keep wondering why you chose
to come back to this school.
Why you reported the bullying right away.
And why you're doing this now.
[music fades]
How much do you know exactly?
[chuckles]
Oh. I'm sorry. That didn't come out right.
If you really are onto something.
then I can tell you everything.
You want the ERPB gone.
That much I do know.
And why is that?
[Hwa-jin] Because of these. I bet.
[tense music plays]
They're called Heart Pills.
Two years ago. they were Butterfly Pills.
-What are the new ones called?
-Diamond.
But you don't have any proof. do you?
If you did. you'd have called the police
and had me arrested.
Yet here you are. talking to me.
You and Ms. Choi Ga-yun
were a match made in heaven.
You're just like her.
Always sticking your nose
into other people's business.
I wonder if you'll end up like her too?
[somber music plays]
[Ga-yun] Mm!
-Finally!
-[Gyu-cheol] Why are you here?
-I told you I'm not going to school.
-Oh. come on.
Did you really think I was just
going to say. "All right. fine. see ya?"
There's no way.
Hey. wait. wait. Come here.
Ugh. you always get hurt somehow
when you skip school.
That looks nasty.
Let me put some ointment on it.
-Please. don't.
-Just stay still.
Oh!
Let's see the other side.
Listen. I don't know what you've been
up to. but come back to school.
It's the safest place for you.
-Do you seriously think that's true?
-I'm not the only one.
There are lots of teachers
trying to make it safe.
We'll do it. I promise you. It'll be safe.
Here. Pinky swear.
-[gasps]
-You can break a finger doing that.
You little shit. Fine. don't come.
But I'm not going anywhere. okay?
I'll follow you around
for the rest of your life.
Think I'm bluffing?
My boyfriend says I'm like a fly trap.
Those sticky ones.
Once I catch you. I don't let go.
I'll pick you up in the morning. Okay?
[sighs]
[Ga-yun sighs]
Mm. Gyu-cheol! Good morning.
No. come on. Hey. Have some.
Gyu-cheol.
-Hey. Come on.
-[man 1] Gyu-cheol!
[Ga-yun] Why are you looking for him?
I'm his teacher.
You're students. right?
-Put those out.
-[man 2] What the fuck?
-Gyu-cheol. come on. Let's go to school.
-[man 2] See you later.
-[Ga-yun] Ignore them.
-We'll call you.
[ominous music plays]
[boy 1] What the hell were you thinking?
You really pissed off those guys
and now they're after your ass.
Is that bitch Choi Ga-yun your girlfriend?
[exhales deeply]
Do you know what Ms. Choi made me realize?
[kids cheer]
[Gyu-cheol] Schools
are packed full of people.
Yeah. so? What else is new?
Imagine if every single one of them
was a customer.
Easy to dodge the cops.
Easy to move the product back and forth.
And the best part?
We'd get hundreds of new customers
every single year.
[boy 2] Pass it. Come on. I'm open!
[sighs]
-[exhales] So cold.
-[Gyu-cheol] Ms. Choi.
[gasps]
Gyu-cheol!
You're in uniform!
I figured I'd dress properly for school
from now on.
Yes. that's the right attitude!
Good for you! Oh!
I won't touch your hair.
You've got your own style.
Have you eaten anything yet?
Wanna grab a bite?
[dramatic music plays]
I BELIEVE IN YOU. GYU-CHEOL!
[Ga-yun groans]
[haunting music plays]
If she'd just pretended she didn't see it.
she would have been your wife by now.
You know?
What are you doing?
You're not planning to hit me. are you?
[boy 1] Hey. the ERPB's here.
[indistinct whispering]
You can't do that.
People are already complaining
about excessive punishment.
If you hit me now. that would come across
as personal revenge.
So just stay still. Don't do it.
If you don't do anything.
nothing will happen to you.
-[groans]
-[students gasp]
[dramatic music plays]
[Gyu-cheol groans]
Man. I'm sorry. Inspector.
-Oh my gosh.
-[Gyu-cheol] I was wrong.
Honest. I'm really sorry.
Please don't hit me anymore.
I'm really sorry. I apologize.
[cries]
It was all my fault.
[cries] Please don't hit me.
I'm really. really sorry.
TEACH YOU A LESSON
-[gasping]
-[Gyu-cheol] Honest. I'm really sorry.
Just please don't hit me anymore.
I'm really sorry.
This is exactly
what I was afraid would happen.
Recently. Lee Chi-ho attempted suicide
over claims of excessive punishment.
and now we're witnessing
Cho Gyu-cheol being assaulted.
Why do you think this happened?
The Bureau went to his school.
and targeted him from the start.
They went there
looking for any excuse to harass him.
This revenge was personal for them.
And in the end.
Mr. Lee Chi-ho was the victim.
I will not tolerate this abuse of power.
I've said before.
the ERPB is driven by personal vendettas.
I will make sure it is dismantled.
[reporter] With public opinion polls
now showing
that 50% of the public
supports dismantling the ERPB.
this has put significant pressure
on the president.
He has been struggling to shake
the lame-duck status he has
in the final stretch of his term.
Despite strong resistance
from the opposition party.
the president has so far
kept the ERPB alive.
But with his approval rating
stuck in the low twenties.
and the pressure he's under to boost it…
I'll come and see you right now.
[girl 1] It's the ERPB!
[somber music plays]
What's the ERPB doing here?
[girl 2] The Bureau
shouldn't go to schools anymore.
We're not potential criminals
or targets for your personal vendettas.
I'm here to investigate Lee Chi-ho's case.
The ERPB's the reason
Chi-ho ended up like that.
Why should they be the ones investigating?
Do you really think that you
can conduct a fair investigation now?
[Gang-seok] Until the investigation
into the suicide attempt
of the student from Jinwon High School
is concluded.
the Educational Rights Protection Bureau
will suspend all duties.
The duties of the ERPB inspectors
will also be put on hold.
ACCESS DENIED
DEPUTY DIRECTOR BONG GEUN-DAE
ERPB
[music fades]
Hey. Everything's all set.
When do we start moving it?
We could start now.
The ERPB's out of the way.
[chuckles]
First. send each school's dealers
samples of the stuff.
Tell them to drum up business with them.
Once a school hits over 100 customers.
that's when the real fun begins
and we start pushing hard.
We're gonna need more runners.
We can't handle all this ourselves.
[tense music plays]
You know. schools
aren't just full of customers.
They've got runners too.
And they're all minors.
No one suspects students.
And even if they get caught.
they'll be released right away.
But. best of all.
they're disposable.
I flip sneakers with this guy
to make some extra cash.
but there are so many scams going on
that people want to meet up
and check them out in person.
All you have to do is just deliver them.
[chuckles]
Okay.
[girl] Hey.
[Seong-gu] Oh. Hi.
SOYEON GIRLS' HIGH SCHOOL
Looks good.
Mm. it's good.
Here.
It was easy. right?
Feel like doing another?
Is that okay?
Of course. I'd really appreciate it.
-[girl] Hey!
-[boy 1] Hey.
-[boy 2] Hi!
-Hey. dude!
You know where to go?
Hey! Hey.
All right. Looks good. Thank you!
I've been making a killing.
It's wild. huh?
[teacher] Genetic diversity.
species diversity…
Oh. Look at all this!
Jin-hyeok. Ju-won.
focus. please!
Within the same species. traits
are determined by genetic information.
And what do we call the part of DNA
that stores that information?
They're called genes.
We're in the middle of class.
What's going on with you today?
Everyone. stay focused. all right?
[suspenseful music plays]
-[girl 1] It looks good.
-[girl 2] Right?
Hey. what is this. art class?
You guys practicing your brushstrokes?
You wouldn't need to use this.
You're pretty. and your face is small.
[girl 2] I'm super jealous.
Come on. I used to have
a round face like you.
[girls chuckle]
-I did. I just lost some weight.
-What did you do?
Was it a diet. or…
I took pills.
They're hard to get.
But try them. If they work. let me know.
-Thanks so much!
-Are you sure?
-Mm-hmm.
-[girl 2] This is awesome!
[girl 3] Did my pitch. Need more samples.
Send some over.
-Oh. Ms. Min--
-Seong-gu!
Seong-jun has been in a motorcycle
accident. I have to go to the hospital.
Tell the kids to have a study period.
Seong-jun got badly hurt
in a motorcycle accident.
Ms. Min's gone to see him.
Holy fuck! Seong-jun's
been running deliveries non-stop.
He managed to buy a bike!
[boy 1] Fuck. really? Let's see.
I'd love one.
Maybe I should boost my runs.
-[boy 1] Get lost!
-[girl] Come on!
-I'm a fucking genius. guys.
-What?
Why don't we just take over
Seong-jun's route?
-How. how. how. how?
-We can do it.
-That's a great idea!
-[boy 2 laughs]
-I can smell the cash.
-I get to go first.
[teacher 1] Don't you feel like
the mood's changed here?
Kids are leaving early or missing school.
and they seem to be so distracted.
[teacher 2 sighs] I'm scared of them.
When the Bureau was around.
we weren't getting respect or anything.
but at least we felt protected in a way.
[sighs] Now. it feels
like we're back to square one.
[somber music plays]
[teacher 1 sighs]
LOOKING FOR ADHD MEDS
OK. CAN DO
NEED BEAUTY PILLS
-Whoa. shit man.
-[cell phone buzzes]
We've got. like. 17 schools in Seoul alone
and about 100 orders from each one.
Pushing those samples
paid off for us. then.
[chuckles]
[cell phone chimes]
[Gyu-cheol sighs]
Let's start really going for it today.
[boy] Okay. Should I blast it
over Telegram?
[suspenseful music plays]
CHO GYU-CHEOL
DROP IT ONCE PAID
[cell phone chimes]
-Can I go and see the nurse?
-[teacher] Mm-hmm.
Miss. I've got a really bad headache.
Uh. Miss. can I be excused? I've got
a bad stomachache. It really hurts.
Huh?
[boy] Uh. Miss.
My grandma's
taken a bad turn.
She's really ill. so I've got to get home.
I'll see you tomorrow.
Ah. shit.
-[girl] Stop pushing!
-[laughter]
-Hey. get moving.
[Gyu-cheol] Hey. Seong-gu.
I saved one for you.
There you go.
[dramatic music plays]
[tense music plays]
[Seong-gu] Inspector Na Hwa-jin.
please call me when you get this message.
I'll be at the convenience store
across the street from school.
[cell phone buzzes]
Hi. Seong-gu.
I'm here in front of the store.
[Seong-gu] I'm sorry. Inspector.
There was something urgent
I needed to do at home.
I just remembered.
so I went straight to my house.
Oh yeah?
Is everything okay?
[Seong-gu] Yeah. it's all good.
[tense music plays]
Yes.
Little fucker.
Tell them to drop the product off. take
pictures. and send them to the customers.
As for this guy…
[Gyu-cheol sighs]
He's a good kid.
What a shame.
[music fades]
[suspenseful music plays]
SOYEON GIRLS' HIGH SCHOOL
[gasps]
You must have been quite surprised.
Inspector Na Hwa-jin
set up this whole operation in secret.
So hitting Cho Gyu-cheol
was part of your plan?
[Hwa-jin] In order for us to get evidence.
Cho Gyu-cheol needed to make a move.
And for that to happen. the ERPB
had to be gone. just like he planned.
[sighs]
[music fades]
Of course. I will take full responsibility
for my actions
once this is over.
I'll take responsibility as well.
My father runs a small gym
and I can always work there. no sweat.
Uh. so. Minister.
you've done so much hard work here
at the Bureau over the past two years.
-Save it.
-[Geun-dae] It's been--
-I'll take responsibility.
-No. you won't.
We all know what a great team you are.
[exhales]
[rock music plays]
I'll be the one to take responsibility.
You all just stick
to the original plan.
Goodbye. sir.
Oh.
So. should we
look into getting backup first?
Like. ask the police to help us.
or something?
The police would be a long shot
without hard evidence.
Besides. they'd be really reluctant
to go into the school. [winces]
All right. then.
we'll. just make it work. that's all.
The three of us can manage.
We'll work around the clock.
Im Han-rim.
what makes you think
it's just the three of us?
[music stops]
This is Choi Gang-seok of the ERPB.
I know.
a lot better than anyone.
just how hard you all work.
Every single day.
you care for your students.
You're standing in for their parents.
That's why it's hard for me to have
to share this difficult news with you.
Unfortunately.
we have confirmed
that there is a new type of drug
being distributed among middle
and high school students
in Seoul presently.
If this drug starts circulating.
then schools
will all suffer irreversible damage.
It will be the students
who will end up paying the ultimate price.
I am therefore asking the teachers
who are watching this video.
for the sake of our children.
please cooperate
and work with the ERPB one more time.
["Fade Into Forever" plays]
We know
you have sacrificed so much.
For that. I am sorry. and ashamed.
I WILL NOT FORGET
YOUR KINDNESS
SAVE CLASSROOMS
SAVE TEACHERS
SCHOOL IS STILL A STRUGGLE
MS. CHOI!
I MISS YOU
I MISS YOUR SMILE SO MUCH
♪ Forever ♪
♪ But I don't feel alone ♪
♪ This is the place I've always known… ♪
YOUR WISHES WILL NOT BE FORGOTTEN
WE WILL HONOR THEM
[Ms. Jung] I agree with the ERPB
that schools must be
safe places for our children.
I'm willing to help them out
any way I can.
♪ Into forever ♪
Here you go.
By the way.
did you hear from any other teachers?
-No one else has reached out yet.
-Ah.
[gentle music plays]
[door opens]
[footsteps approach]
[uplifting music plays]
These pills were all collected by us
at our schools.
[music fades]
[Gang-seok] I know
it couldn't have been easy.
Thank you for this.
But what happens if
this drug is already in circulation?
Don't you worry about that.
It will never happen.
Right?
Right.
♪ Listen. and learn
And listen. and learn ♪
♪ And listen. and learn ♪
-He's out. he's out.
-Oh. there he is.
♪ And learn. and listen. and learn ♪
♪ And listen. and learn. r-r-r-repeat ♪
♪ Listen. and learn
And listen. and learn ♪
♪ And listen. and learn… ♪
-God.
-[Han-rim groans]
All right. See ya later.
Oh. wait. hold on.
Uh…
Here it is.
Come here.
♪ Listen. and learn… ♪
Mm.
-Okay?
-Beautiful.
[Han-rim] Bye!
These vitamins are so cool. They help you
lose weight and they're nutritional.
-Does it mean we'll look like Yu-ri?
-[girl 1] I sure hope so.
[girl 2] I wanna lose ten pounds.
-[Han-rim] There.
-[Geun-dae] I see them.
[Han-rim] Get ready.
Whoa. Wh… what do I do?
When they come out here.
hit me in the head.
-A slap?
-No. Like in the face?
[Geun-dae groans]
Wait. Not in the head!
[groans]
-I'm sorry!
-[Han-rim] You little shit!
-Hey. Where do you think you're going?
-[groans] Run! Get outta here!
If you don't have any money…
[Geun-dae groans]
…then give me something valuable.
like your phone.
-[Geun-dae] Okay!
-Your watch!
-[Geun-dae coughs]
-Or vitamin C. asshole.
[Geun-dae] Yeah. okay. I've got some.
-Yeah?
-I've got some in here.
[Han-rim] Vitamin C?
-Yeah. Here. take it.
-Hey. look. Take ours.
[girl] This is all we have.
I'll follow the student in front
over there.
I'll take the one with the brown backpack.
What about the rest?
Don't worry about them.
I called in backup.
Some kids that used to
know how to shake people down.
Huh?
♪ And listen. and learn.
And listen. and learn ♪
♪ And listen. and learn. and listen… ♪
We've collected
all the sample drugs. okay?
Now moving on to the next step.
[Geun-dae] I'll message them on Telegram
and place the order.
♪ And listen. and learn ♪
♪ And listen. and learn
And listen. and learn ♪
[Han-rim] Wow!
[computer chimes]
[music fades]
This is a new drug
that's been circulating among students.
It's a substitute for the Heart Pill
that was recently classified
as a controlled substance.
These were discovered on school grounds
by teachers at various schools
and brought to
the Educational Rights Protection Bureau.
After tracing the distribution route.
we have now identified the main dealer
as Cho Gyu-cheol of Jinwon High School.
So. as of this moment.
the suspension of the Bureau's duties
has been lifted.
-All inspectors will be returning to work.
-Shit.
Damn it.
[rock music plays]
♪ I'm gonna hunt you down… ♪
-Hey. can you do this?
-Yeah. hold on.
♪ I'mma take your crown… ♪
Thanks.
[Gang-seok] We have now
identified the main dealer
as Cho Gyu-cheol of Jinwon High School.
[boy] Look. it's the ERPB.
-♪ I'm gonna hunt you down ♪
-♪ Gonna hunt you down ♪
-♪ Yeah. I ain't playing around ♪
-♪ Ain't playing around ♪
♪ I'mma take your crown ♪
♪ Man. better run. gonna hunt you down ♪
♪ Yeah. I be coming for you
Like Hannibal ♪
-[music stops]
-[Geun-dae] Whoa!
Oh. [strains]
[sighs] Give it to me. I'll do it.
[Geun-dae] Whoa! Hey. be careful.
[suspenseful music plays]
Oh! Inspector Im. this one won't open.
Don't open it!
[gasps] Oh!
[Hwa-jin] Hold your breath! Don't inhale!
[dramatic music plays]
Are you okay?
[Han-rim exhales]
[coughs]
[tense music plays]
[boy 1] Hey. guys.
Looks like they fell for the trap.
[boy 2] Did you get a taste?
Fucking sweet. huh?
Let me know if you want more!
-[boy 1] Hey!
-[boy 2] Fucking asshole!
-That idiot will never get us.
-Jackass.
[Han-rim] I'll catch them.
[boy 2] Come on.
Let's get the fuck out of here.
[dramatic music plays]
Hey. guess what?
I can fly!
What?
Im Han-rim. preparing final descent.
-Yeah!
-Oh!
-[Han-rim screams]
-Whoa!
-[Han-rim laughs]
-[boys groan]
-[boy 2] Shit!
-[boy 1] Goddamn it
-[boy 2 winces]
-[boy 1] Ow. my head.
[boy 2 groans]
[boy 2] Holy shit.
-[boy 2 groans]
-[boy 1] Oh. fuck.
-[running footsteps approach]
-[groaning]
[boy 2] Ow. my back. [groans]
Im Han-rim. you okay?
[boy 2 groans]
[Hwa-jin] Han-rim?
[music fades]
Don't worry about me. sir. Keep going.
Huh.
[imitates trumpet fanfare]
[imitates trumpet]
Shit.
I'll take care of Inspector Im. sir.
You go ahead.
Go on. go on. hurry.
-[boy 1] Holy shit.
-Okay. yeah.
-[boy 2] Fuck. I thought I was gonna die.
-[boy 1] This bitch is fucking nuts.
[imitates trumpet]
-Oh shit.
-I can be an angel.
Or I can be a devil. you know?
It all depends on how I feel at the time.
I'm going to be
a devil now.
[rock music plays]
-[boy 2] Oh fuck.
-Ha!
[boy 1 gasps]
-[boy 1] It's a real knife!
-[boy 2] Go!
[boy 1] Oh fuck!
[music stops]
You boneheads!
[Han-rim grunts]
-[boy 1] Wow.
-Move!
[boy 2] She must be high.
[boys laugh]
-[boy 2] She's totally out of it!
-[boy 1] Shit!
Come on. Try and hit me.
[boy 2 laughs]
[boy 1] Take that. you little… [grunts]
[boy 2] You fucking little bitch.
-So. you're a fucking angel now?
-[Geun-dae] Leave her alone!
[Han-rim] It hurts!
[intriguing music plays]
You goddamn piece of shit!
-Oh!
-[boy 2] Think you can beat us. asshole?
[boy 1] Stupid prick!
Fucking pig!
[Geun-dae yells]
Oh!
Inspector Im! Are you okay?
[sighs]
Are… are you hurt at all?
[music stops]
So damn cute.
-What?
-[Han-rim sighs]
Oh!
[tense music plays]
-[boy 3] Hey!
-[boy 4] Where d'you think you're going?
-Hey. you! Asshole.
-Me?
Look. let's make this quick. all right?
I'll hit each of you one time. That's it.
[boy 5] Fuck!
Fucker!
[boys groan]
[groans]
Do you know how dangerous this thing is.
you little shit?
[music fades]
-[Geun-dae] Why don't we sit down?
-[Han-rim] Sorry.
-Sorry.
-You're good.
-I'm good.
-You got it.
-I can do it. Keep going.
-[Geun-dae] Whoa! Sit here.
Whoa. watch it. Easy now.
-[sighs]
-Are you feeling dizzy? Are you?
-Whoa. whoa. What should I do?
[tense music plays]
Well. shit. man.
It's just like last time.
[breathes shakily]
What are you doing with this?
Why didn't you call the police on me?
I really wanted
to give you another chance.
but you must
turn yourself in.
So. you haven't told anyone about it yet?
This chance that you've given me.
I'll make the best of it.
Gyu-cheol. [gasps]
You really don't fucking know
anything about me. do you?
[gasps]
[Gyu-cheol] Why would I turn myself in?
I'm a minor.
I'll be out in no time.
If they charge me with manslaughter.
I'll only get two years. maximum.
I come from a broken home.
I had no motive at all.
And to top it all off…
I was in love with you this whole time.
Gyu-cheol. you don't--
-[knife slices]
-[Ga-yun gasps]
-[flesh squelches]
-[groans]
[Ga-yun groans]
[Ga-yun gasps]
I can always come back
and just sell this in two years.
[Ga-yun breathes shakily]
Thanks to you. I came back to school
and realized this is the hottest market.
Too bad. though.
Guess you won't be getting married now.
You can't do that. [gasps]
[Ga-yun breathes shakily]
[groans]
Guess I'm no match for an ERPB inspector.
[sighs]
I'm sorry about everything.
Yeah.
I'll hit you once then.
but it is going to hurt.
I wouldn't move if I were you.
or another innocent person
might end up dying at this school.
-[Seong-gu] No. don't!
-[boy 6] Get moving. you fucking asshole!
[Seong-gu whimpers]
[Seong-gu breathes shakily]
[Seong-gu gasps] No!
[Seong-gu sobs]
[dramatic music plays]
Inspector Na!
[breathes shakily]
-[grunts]
-What are you doing? Hold on!
Whoa. are you okay?
[groans]
[Geun-dae] What?
[shrieks]
[Seong-gu whimpers]
[tense music plays]
I'll let Seong-gu live
when you go see your beloved fiancée.
Please tell her that
I'm really sorry.
[Gyu-cheol breathes heavily]
[Gyu-cheol grunts]
[Seong-gu sobs]
[screams]
[dramatic music plays]
[boy 6] Hey.
Look at him.
[Seong-gu sobs]
[Hwa-jin sighs]
-[knife slides]
-[Gyu-cheol breathes heavily]
[tense music plays]
[Gyu-cheol breathes heavily]
-[knife slices]
-[Seong-gu] Stop!
Please. stop it!
[Gyu-cheol grunts]
[knife slices]
[dramatic music plays]
[Geun-dae] Oh my God!
[screams]
[breathes shakily]
[Han-rim screams]
I need to sober up. Help me sober up.
-[Geun-dae] What?
-Do something!
[Han-rim screams]
[Gyu-cheol] This isn't gonna fly in court
as self-defense.
or as manslaughter.
I'll have to move out of the country.
Huh?
There are schools all over the world.
[groans]
[classical music plays]
[music stops]
-[boy 6 groans]
-[knife clatters]
[boy 6] Ah. fuck!
[Seong-gu whimpers]
[boy 6] You shit!
[boy 6 yells]
-Who the fuck are you?
-[Han-rim] Who am I?
Inspector Im Han-rim of the ERPB.
Agh. you fucking bitch! [groans]
[rock music plays]
[Gyu-cheol] Let go.
I said let go. you fucking--
[exhales]
-[strains]
-You like running your mouth off.
Hm?
Gonna let me talk now?
[exhales]
[groans]
[Hwa-jin exhales]
Oh!
Go ahead.
♪ You say we are small
So you think we are weak ♪
♪ Well. you might be right
But we are ready to fight… ♪
Agh!
[groans]
That was a bad choice. Hm?
You just blew another chance.
♪ Chihuahua. chihuahua ♪
[knife clatters]
♪Chihuahua. chihuahua… ♪
[Gyu-cheol groans]
[Hwa-jin] Listen to me carefully.
Everyone in this country
has the right to an equal education
to the extent of their abilities.
and through that.
the right to be happy!
That is what
kids come to school for.
Now.
any bastard that gets in the way of that…
no matter who.
has to be taught a lesson.
[grunts]
[groans]
[music fades]
[Gyu-cheol whimpers]
I'm sorry.
Please don't kill me.
-I have no intention of doing that.
-[Gyu-cheol] I'm really sorry.
Please give me another chance.
Chances aren't something you're given.
You earn them when you truly want them.
[Ga-yun] I wanted
to give you a chance.
[poignant music plays]
You know. Gyu-cheol.
the thing is.
chances aren't something you're given.
You earn them when you truly want them.
-[knife slices]
-[Ga-yun gasps]
[Gyu-cheol] Wow.
You two were really made for each other.
[haunting music plays]
[Gyu-cheol chuckles]
Do you know what Choi Ga-yun said
before she died?
"Gyu-cheol.
you can't do that."
[groans]
What the fuck did she mean. I can't?
Don't give me that!
You don't fucking care about me.
I don't need a stupid chance.
Just kill me. all right?
Go on.
Do it!
[strains]
I said do it now!
[Gyu-cheol breathes shakily]
[Hwa-jin breathes shakily]
[breathes shakily]
[exhales]
Gyu-cheol.
I can't do that.
It's okay.
[Gyu-cheol cries]
Let's start over. then.
Mm-hmm.
[Gyu-cheol cries]
[sobs]
This is the last chance
Ms. Choi Ga-yun will ever give you.
[sobs]
[poignant music plays]
Oh fuck!
Who the hell do you people think you are?
You think you're Jesus Christ?
Fucking Buddha or some shit?
[Hwa-jin grunts]
[Gyu-cheol sobs]
[breathes shakily]
We're adults. punk. That's all.
[Gyu-cheol cries]
[exhales]
I did well. right?
[inaudible]
[cries]
[sobs]
[exhales]
[music fades]
[footsteps approach]
[panting]
[uplifting music plays]
Should I get you a stapler?
[laughs]
Ah. shit.
Don't make me laugh. [chuckles]
♪ Simple as us… ♪
[boy 1] Watch it. all right?
-[boy 2] Stop fucking pushing!
-[officer 1] Stop resisting.
[Geun-dae] You're gonna be fine. [sighs]
[officer 2] Keep walking.
-[boy 3] Let go of me!
-[boy 1] I get it!
-[officer 1] Get in.
-[boy 3] Ow. fuck.
You're being charged
with violations against the ERPB Act.
the Controlled Substances Act.
attempted murder…
and…
and several violations
of the Punishment of Violences Act.
As of this moment.
you are expelled from Jinwon High School.
You will never
return to this school ever again.
Take him away.
The Bureau will proceed
according to protocol.
[officers] Yes. sir.
[music fades]
[car door closes]
Hm.
Oh!
[Gang-seok] Hey. what happened?
Huh?
-You got stabbed?
-Yeah. I'm fine.
-[Geun-dae] You okay?
-A few stitches.
-Cho Gyu-cheol. you bastard! You did this?
-Stop him!
-You son of a…
-Whoa!
-He's my son-in-law! Come out!
-Stop!
-[Gang-seok] You little shit!
-[Han-rim] Stop!
-You stabbed my son-in-law?
-Go. go. go!
-[Gang-seok] Come out of there!
-You've got to let him go!
-I'll get you. you punk! Hey!
-Whoa. whoa!
-[yells] You're killing me!
-[Han-rim groans]
Minister!
-[Hwa-jin groans]
-He's okay.
MINISTRY OF EDUCATION
[Gang-seok] My fellow citizens.
do you know the meaning of education?
"The teaching of knowledge. skills.
and the cultivation of character."
That is what a true education is.
Good universities and good jobs
are important.
but what is more essential
is nurturing a person's integrity
and their moral compass as well.
That is the kind of education
we need to strive for.
And yet. today.
Korea's education system
has strayed far from that purpose.
and is broken.
[poignant music plays]
Nonetheless. in the midst of all this.
most teachers in our country
continue to excel at their jobs.
They keep teaching our children and strive
to guide them on the right path.
How much longer do we have to see
our students
and our incredible teachers
go off to their schools
and never make it back home?
Until schools are no longer
places of fear
and anxiety…
this Bureau
will uphold the value of education.
and protect victims.
Until Korea's education system
is restored to what it once was…
we will be here.
I MISS YOUR SMILE SO MUCH
[Gang-seok] Good for you. Ga-yun. honey.
There's so many people
who remember you dearly.
THE LATE CHOI GA-YUN
You need this?
Hey. I'm not a crying man.
I'm a man without tears. [chuckles]
-I heard you've shed a lot of tears.
-[Gang-seok chuckles]
-Who told you that?
-Ga-yun did.
Ha! You're joking.
She told me that. uh.
you cried the day that the stray cat
you were taking care of got adopted.
-She said you wept for a month.
-That's not…
Oh!
That's actually kinda sweet.
He's very sweet. He's got
a lot of love in him. And many tears.
-That's adorable. sir.
-I can't believe you.
Hey. listen.
Did you finish that report on Jinwon High?
I want that report now!
-He just turned into our boss. again.
-Is that even okay?
[Hwa-jin] Workplace harassment.
Harassment. my ass.
If you don't wanna work. just say so.
But if you've got a beef.
we can settle this another way.
[Geun-dae] Let me check
and get back to you. Bye.
Listen up. We've got a lot of work
to do and not much time.
I can't be the only working.
Uh. Minister. fists down. please.
-Let's get going. Come on. Inspector Im.
-[Han-rim] All right.
[Geun-dae] Come on.
-[Gang-seok] He's really scaring me.
-[Hwa-jin] Same here.
Every time he sees me.
he asks for a report. It's tiring.
He acts like he's the boss.
Have you sent in the Jinwon High report?
I'll do it today. if that's okay?
Don't just stand there. Come on!
-We're coming.
-Yeah. okay.
And. Minister. you can't raise your fists
to an employee like that. ever. okay?
[chuckles]
Oh. watch.
Yeah.
-[yelps]
-Oh!
What's wrong? What?
-You held my hand.
-[Geun-dae] Oh.
Well. there was a rock there
and I thought you might fall.
Still. why would you do that?
You held mine last time.
No. I didn't. No.
Jeez. I let you hold my hand
and I get told off.
-You let me?
-What?
-You "let me" hold it?
-What's going on?
-[Han-rim] Why did you say it like that?
-They really like each other.
But they don't seem to know it yet.
Ah!
[Han-rim] I need to sober up.
Please help me!
-[Geun-dae] What should I do?
-Help me!
-Like what?
-[Han-rim] I don't know. Something.
-Just please do something!
-[Geun-dae] But what?
Hold on. Just a second! Sorry!
♪ From the day I found you ♪
[Han-rim] Still. why hold my hand?
-Well. I did let you--
-[Han-rim] Again with the "let me."
[Geun-dae] Guys. hurry up.
You're lagging behind.
-[Gang-seok] All right.
-[Hwa-jin] Keep your shirt on.
-Should we hold hands too?
-[Gang-seok] What? No way!
[Hwa-jin] Why are you getting flustered?
Feeling a bit lonely?
-[Geun-dae] Stop chatting. Get a move on!
-[Hwa-jin] We're coming!
[music fades]
[thwacking]
ASIAN GAMES BASKETBALL
SEO TAE-HUN WINS GOLD
Next.
Next!
Move quicker. you asshole.
Ugh. you fucking idiots.
You guys get all the perks
because of me. huh?
Right. you little fucker?
Yeah.
You're all going to Hanguk University
'cause I got scouted.
Like a fucking
two-for-the-price-of-one deal. huh?
And you fuckers don't even pay me back?
If I'm not making real money in the pros.
you should make up for that.
[sighs]
Whatever.
If you don't have the money.
then you're gonna pay this way.
Yeah.
[Geun-dae] Stop!
[rock music plays]
You boys are all high school students.
You should be studying.
Hey. guys. Get up.
I said get up. It's okay. Don't worry.
Come on. Up.
I'm Deputy Director Bong Geun-dae
of the ERPB.
And. right now.
the ERPB
is going to teach you a lesson.
Come on. guys.
Stand up.
You can get back in line.
I said stand.
[tense music plays]
Yeah?
-Hey. you told me to stand.
-Hey!
Let go! I said let go.
-You said stand up.
-I said let go.
-[boy] No. stand up.
-[Geun-dae] Let go.
-You told me to stand.
-Let go.
Take your hands off him right now!
Who's that?
-[boys gasp]
-Stand up.
[boys mutter]
I said stand!
♪ And listen. and learn… ♪
If you listen to what we say.
we teach with words.
And if a heavy hand is all that you need.
you'll have to learn the hard way.
♪ Listen. and learn
And listen. and learn ♪
♪ And listen. and learn ♪
[Han-rim grunts]
[both groan]
-[Geun-dae] You okay?
-[Han-rim] I'm fine. You okay?
-[Geun-dae] You're sure?
-Piece of shit.
[Geun-dae] Whoa! Don't!
Stop. come on. don't!
You think this is funny?
-[Geun-dae] You'll get hurt!
-[Han-rim] No. I won't!
Well. well. well. well.
Would you look at this sorry bunch?
You're athletes. but you're putting up
with this crap instead of training.
Even with the Bureau here.
you still don't know how to behave?
Huh?
[rock music plays]
Well?
Students have no authority
in school whatsoever.
Not even athletes
representing the country.
You may or may not know this.
but the newly-revived ERPB
has no limits on our
education methods.
So from this moment on…
I'll be teaching you a lesson.
♪ Chihuahua. chihuahua ♪
♪ Chihuahua… ♪
TEACH YOU A LESSON
♪ You say we are small
So you think we are weak ♪
♪ Well. you might be right
But we are ready to fight ♪
♪ We've got brains
Also. we are fearless ♪
♪ Don't mess with us
Or you are dead meat ♪
♪ We look pretty cute
But don't judge us by that ♪
♪ We bark like thunder
And we move like wind ♪
♪ Did you say we're small?
Do you still think we are weak? ♪
All right.
♪ Chihuahua… ♪
You think it's all over for me?
[groans]
-[woman] Mr. Hwang!
-[Gi-tae groans]
-[officer 1] Let's get him up.
-[officer 2] Come on.
[Gi-tae groans]
I'll… be back. I'm warning you.
You'll be the first I bring down.
♪ We are small. chihuahua. chihuahua… ♪
You knew what really happened
when Cho Gyu-cheol
gave you the recording.
You should have stopped it then.
It's people like you
who turn young students into monsters.
You might not be capable of being good.
but you should've known better.
What about you?
You think you're so righteous?
I'm sure there are skeletons
in your closet! Huh?
[music fades]
[sniffs]
[rock music plays]
[Gang-seok] Hmm.
And so.
I'm not really
a good person either.
-[Gang-seok grunts]
-[screams in pain]
[Gi-tae groans]
-Ow!
-[officer 3] What the…
[Gi-tae groans]
-Oh.
-Oh my goodness! Did you see that?
[laughs]
♪ Chihuahua. chihuahua ♪
♪ Chihuahua ♪
♪ We are cute ♪
♪ Chihuahua. chihuahua ♪
♪ Chihuahua ♪
♪ We are smart ♪
♪ Chihuahua. chihuahua ♪
♪ Chihuahua ♪
♪ We are small ♪
♪ Chihuahua. chihuahua ♪
♪ Chihuahua ♪
♪ But we are strong ♪
[music fades]
Support us and become VIP member
to remove all ads from www.OpenSubtitles.org